{
  "decks": [
    {
      "name": "React Router",
      "description": "React Router is a collection of navigational components that compose declaratively with your application.",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "name": "JavaScript",
      "description": "Java questions",
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "name": "Test Deck",
      "description": "Random workspace deck",
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "name": "Jessica's Questions ",
      "description": "Cosmo stuff",
      "id": 5
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "What path will match the follow Route?\n<Route>\n  <NotFound />\n</Route>",
      "back": "All paths. A route with no path matches all URL's",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 4
    },
    {
      "front": "What does <Switch> do?",
      "back": "Renders the first matching child <Route> ",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 5
    },
    {
      "front": "Who is the coolest JS coder",
      "back": "YOU! ",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 6
    },
    {
      "front": "What program are you in right now?",
      "back": "Thinkful Bootcamp",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "front": "What is better Mercedes or Lambo?",
      "back": "Ferrari",
      "deckId": 3,
      "id": 8
    },
    {
      "front": "E=? ",
      "back": "E=mc2",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 10
    },
    {
      "front": "what is 2+2? ",
      "back": "4",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 11
    },
    {
      "front": "Where can you obtain water?",
      "back": "In the sea ",
      "deckId": 4,
      "id": 12
    },
    {
      "front": "How much time does a color process take? ",
      "back": "45 min ",
      "deckId": 5,
      "id": 14
    },
    {
      "front": "Where did i got to cosmo school?",
      "back": "MATC",
      "deckId": 5,
      "id": 15
    },
    {
      "front": "yes?",
      "back": "Ok",
      "deckId": 2,
      "id": 16
    }
  ]
}